mymajors.com 2006-12-31

# Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement for MyMajors.com

* * *

_Acceptance of Terms/Changes to Privacy Policy_ : Your use of this site indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy. Mymajors.com reserves the right to update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. 

_Disclaimer:_ Mymajors.com provides recommendations and information on college and university majors. It creates some of the information and third parties may create some. While MyMajors.com strives to provide helpful advice, commentary and other information, Mymajors.com does not make any warranty regarding the accuracy, reliability or use of any information provided on this site, including major information, or major recommendations. Users should consider the system’s recommendations in the context of many other factors such as parental recommendations, high school and college counselor recommendations, aptitude test results and your own motivations, among other factors.

MyMajors.com shares your concerns about privacy. Since an essential function of this site is to evaluate your interests and abilities, largely based upon the information you provide, we want you to understand what types of information we are collecting and what may happen to that information. 

Mymajors.com will not knowingly sell, share, rent or otherwise transfer your information other than in accordance with the terms set forth in this Policy.

The MyMajors.com website may be linked to by other sites and it has links to other sites. MyMajors.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites. Check each website's privacy policy before giving out any personal information.

The effectiveness of MyMajors.com requires that we collect personal information from its users in order to make useful recommendations. This data is used only to make these recommendations to the user and to help us to evaluate and improve the system to make it better.

MyMajors.com gathers personal information primarily through screens you see. We do not retrieve information from your computer. 

MyMajors.com does not share, sell, or rent personally identifiable information, including your email address, with outside third parties without your express consent. 

The MyMajors.com attempts to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. System security breaches by outside parties may be beyond our control, so MyMajors.com requires a username and password combination to enable you to reuse the system without having to reenter all of the data you entered during the first usage. Do not divulge your password or login name to anyone else. 

MyMajors.com constantly monitors systems for unauthorized use. Tools employed to minimize hacking attempts include firewall systems, periodic administrator password rotations, continuous review and implementation of third-party security updates, virtual private network solutions, point-to-point tunneling protocols, and log file analyses.

Within the system, students only have access to their own demographic information. One student cannot access private information about another student. Staff of MyMajors.com has limited access to this data for system testing and system evaluation purposes. 

Upon request, any information you enter can be deleted from our database.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:
